<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christian Parenting on HanaBustillos.com</title>
    <link>hanabustillos.com/tags/christian-parenting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christian Parenting on HanaBustillos.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="hanabustillos.com/tags/christian-parenting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Raising Children in God’s Care: All Things to All People</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/blog/all-things-all-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/blog/all-things-all-people/</guid>
      <description>Mothers often feel like they are everything to their children, but also struggle with the fear of failure and the guilt of imperfection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Myth of the To-Do List: How to Stop Measuring God’s Love by YOUR Success</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/blog/to-do-myth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/blog/to-do-myth/</guid>
      <description>Being a parent is a tough job, and I&amp;rsquo;ve learned that no matter how much we plan, there are always things that don&amp;rsquo;t go according to plan. I used to get frustrated when things didn&amp;rsquo;t work out, but I&amp;rsquo;ve come to realize that it&amp;rsquo;s okay to fail sometimes. Even when I mess up, I know that I&amp;rsquo;m still loved and accepted by God, and that gives me the strength to keep going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motherhood and Mirrors: Balancing Motherhood and Self-Reflection</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/blog/motherhood-and-mirrors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/blog/motherhood-and-mirrors/</guid>
      <description>A call to action for mothers to persevere, reflecting their faith in their actions, even when it’s hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Clay and the Potter: What Isaiah 45 Teaches Us About Parenting</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/blog/pottery-parenting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/blog/pottery-parenting/</guid>
      <description>Our kids need us to respect their individuality and autonomy, while also helping to shape them. ⁤⁤We may feel fear and guilt since we don&amp;rsquo;t have complete control over the outcome. ⁤⁤We can do our best and trust in God&amp;rsquo;s grace and wisdom to guide us and our children through life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting 1001</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/blog/goal-setting-1001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/blog/goal-setting-1001/</guid>
      <description>Reflections on my experience with the 101 in 1001 goal-setting format. I found that the format was not realistic for my life as a mom of three small children with limited free time. As a busy mom, I struggled to find time for myself amidst child care, homeschooling, laundry, grocery shopping, cleaning, and other daily tasks. I&amp;rsquo;m now on the hunt for a more flexible goal-setting method that works better for my busy schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wooden Spoon Motherhood: Finding Joy in the Simple and Functional</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/blog/timothy-letters-five/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/blog/timothy-letters-five/</guid>
      <description>Motherhood feels like we’re always using the utensils made from wood and clay, the ordinary, everyday utensils that we don’t mind scuffing up.  We may turn to the same tools all the time - wearing the same basic outfit, or serving the same few meals.  As long as it works for us, that’s the most important thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God Did Not Give us a Spirit of Cowardice</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/blog/timothy-letters-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/blog/timothy-letters-four/</guid>
      <description>You have been gifted by God for motherhood and you have enough power, love, and self-discipline to overcome fears of being a bad mother. We are not alone in this journey and we can rely on God and those who care about us. You can do this with God&amp;rsquo;s help and grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spiritual Exercise and the Humbling Experience of Motherhood</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/blog/timothy-letters-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/blog/timothy-letters-three/</guid>
      <description>The apostle Paul tells us to not only take care of our bodies, but also work on our spiritual fitness. He advises us to avoid negative influences and pursue godliness, which is valuable for both this life and the next. He also warns us that our journey will not be smooth sailing, and we have to face it with faith and hope in God, who is our Savior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modeling a Relationship with God for Our Children</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/blog/timothy-letters-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/blog/timothy-letters-two/</guid>
      <description>Just as Paul was &amp;lsquo;foremost&amp;rsquo; in the early church - the one who was displaying his life as an example to others, as mothers, we are often foremost in our child’s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating New Motherhood: The Unspoken Resentment</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/blog/matthew_11_navigating/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/blog/matthew_11_navigating/</guid>
      <description>Mothers live in and through moments of strong emotions, both positive and negative.  It’s common for mothers to grapple with resentment, a constant feeling of imbalance, and the weight of unmet needs. In our vulnerability, we find solace in knowing that God, in His boundless compassion, doesn’t judge us for these emotions. He holds our deepest feelings, offering comfort,  understanding, and peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Feel Qualified to be a Mom? You&#39;re in Good Company</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/blog/timothy-letters-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/blog/timothy-letters-one/</guid>
      <description>Motherhood is a beautiful and challenging journey that can leave many women feeling unprepared. However, the Bible is full of stories of God choosing people who felt unqualified for the task at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
