<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HanaBustillos.com</title>
    <link>hanabustillos.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HanaBustillos.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="hanabustillos.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Joys of Motherhood Volume 1</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/en/blog/joys-motherhood-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/en/blog/joys-motherhood-1/</guid>
      <description>Photo by energepic.com from Pexels: Motherhood comes with its share of struggles, and obviously that makes up most of my content. However, it also comes with its share of joys, and most of the time, the joys outweigh the struggles with no contest. This series is a little respite from the “hard stuff” that I write about. It’s a time and space to celebrate the things that make raising children so wonderful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Starting This Blog</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/en/blog/why-starting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 14:50:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/en/blog/why-starting/</guid>
      <description>I’ve had a lot of job experience in writing devotions, sermons, prayers, and keynotes, that (hopefully) were meaningful to people and reminded them that God loves them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mother&#39;s Day Prayer</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/en/blog/mothers-day-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/en/blog/mothers-day-prayer/</guid>
      <description>This pastoral prayer covers a lot of situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Can Separate Us</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/en/blog/romans-8-38-39/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/en/blog/romans-8-38-39/</guid>
      <description>Mistakes, challenges, and failings will not separate you from the God who loves you no matter what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/en/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/en/page/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a blog for overwhelmed moms.
Moms who feel like they have made mistakes.
Moms who feel like they don’t know what they’re doing.
Moms who think they have failed their kids.
This blog is a place for you to find rest, comfort, and solidarity. A place where you can get in touch with God, yourself, and your own wonderful, flawed humanity - as a mom and as a person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help, Thanks, Wow</title>
      <link>hanabustillos.com/en/blog/romans-12-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>hanabustillos.com/en/blog/romans-12-help/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Tatiana Syrikova from Pexels: &amp;lt;img src=&amp;#34;https://www.pexels.com/photo/crop-mother-and-daughter-using-laptop-and-drawing-3975640.jpeg&amp;#34; alt=&amp;#34;laptop on bed&amp;#34;&amp;gt; I call this a “Help, Thanks, Wow” prayer, based on Anne Lamot’s Book of the same name, which posits that those are the three essential prayers. Romans 12 is so rich in reminders of both God’s unconditional love and God’s will for us to always strive for better. But - not better as the world sees it. Not better as in, you are only a perfect mother if you (fill in the blank with whatever instagram is telling you - have an unmedicated birth, discipline a certain way, only eat certain foods, lose all the baby weight in a prescribed amount of time, whatever).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
